Mateusz Tomczyk



Contact

Phone:

+48 509 205 358

Email:

mateusztomczyk1996@gmail.com

Languages

Polish – Native language English – Advanced (C1)

Summary

Frontend Developer specializing in React applications. Experienced with many projects in typical frontend stack (HTML + CSS + JavaScript) and other in React + Redux (with SCSS), for different clients, ranging from small entrepreneurs to large corporations such as Sabre.

Skill Highlights

- HTML5
- JavaScript
- React + Redux
- Jest + Enzyme
- Git
- Problem Solving
- Web Development
- Web Applications

- CSS3
- SCSS
- Experience with Jenkins and Travis, used for CI
- Experience with docker
- Typescript

Experience

Frontend Developer - 05/2019 to 05/2020 Relyon IT Services, Warsaw

Working in Sabre Poland as a contractor

Frontend Developer - 05/2019 to 05/2020 Sabre Poland, Cracow

- Working here as a contractor from Relyon IT Services
- Developing an application for reservations, used by clients and airport agents for many different airlines such as Aeroflot or Virgin Australia
- Tech stack: React, Redux, SCSS, HTML5, Jest + Enzyme for unit tests, TestCafe for automation tests, Jenkins, Git

Junior Frontend Developer - 02/2018 to 05/2019 **Bravelab Software House**, Cracow

- Developing a few applications for different clients in Poland, as well as in United States
- Few examples of clients: IMS, Symplete, Förk it,
- Tech stack: HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Wordpress, Angular, React, Redux, React Native, Travis, Git

Junior Frontend Developer - 08/2017 to 02/2018 evl.pl, Cracow

- Creating a wide range of landing pages and applications for many different clients, banners and mailings for InPost
- Few examples of clients (apart from InPost and DHL): nowaklighting.eu, endorwina.pl
- Tech stack: HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Wordpress, Git

Frontend Developer - 06/2016 to 08/2016

Man La Mode inc, Ann Arbor, MI (remotely from Cracow)

- First serious commercial job as a frontend developer
- Creating a shop for clothing companies
- Tech stack: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

Intern - 08/2015 to 09/2015

ESC SA, Cracow

- Internship for summer break in 2015.
- First major experience with frontend development
- Helping with updating pages for cities like Konstancinjeziorna or Zakopane
- Tech stack: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, VelaCMS

Intern - 04/2015 to 05/2015

PressPad, Cracow

- Mandatory school internship.
- Creating a mobile app in java for fashion magazines with help of experienced developers

Education

College Of Economics And Computer Science

October 2017 – now, Cracow Engineering studies with 'Web & Mobile Applications Development' profile.

Languages

- Polish native language
- English advanced level

Hobbies

- Music
- Art
- Lego
- Video Games
- Travelling around the world

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).